Guide to the Arthur M. Schlesinger, Jr. papers, 1922-2007
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series IV: Research Files, 385866; 142 boxes
  - Subseries IV. B. Book Files, 1940s-1990s; 386180; 69 boxes
    - Age of Roosevelt, 386181
      - Subjects, 386182
        - Hyde Park, 386304 (Box 452, Folder 6)
        - Ickes, Harold, 386305 (Box 452, Folder 7)
        - If, 386306 (Box 452, Folder 8)
        - Inaugurations, 386307
          - 1933, 386308 (Box 452, Folder 9)
          - 1937, 386309 (Box 452, Folder 10)
        - India, 386310 (Box 452, Folder 11)
        - Indians, 386311 (Box 452, Folder 12)
        - Industrial unionism, 386312 (Box 452, Folder 13)
        - Intellectuals, 386313 (Box 452, Folder 14-15)
        - Intelligence operations, 386314 (Box 453, Folder 1)
        - Iran, 386315 (Box 453, Folder 2)
        - Isolationism, 386316 (Box 453, Folder 3)
        - Isolationists, 386317 (Box 453, Folder 4-5)
        - Italy, 386318 (Box 453, Folder 6)
        - Japan, 386319 (Box 454, Folder 1-4)
        - Japanese internment, 386320 (Box 454, Folder 5)
        - Journalism, 386321 (Box 454, Folder 6)
        - Keynes, John Maynard, et al., 386322 (Box 454, Folder 7)
        - Labor, 386323 (Box 454, Folder 8-9)
        - LaFollette, Philip, 386324 (Box 454, Folder 10)
        - Landon campaign, 386325 (Box 454, Folder 11)
        - Landon campaign, 386326 (Box 455, Folder 1)
        - Latin America, 386327 (Box 455, Folder 2-6)
        - Law and foreign policy, 386328 (Box 455, Folder 7-8)
        - Lend-Lease, 386329 (Box 455, Folder 9)
        - Liberal economic theory, 386330 (Box 456, Folder 1)
        - Liberalism in the 1920s, 386331 (Box 456, Folder 2)
        - Liberals in wartime, 386332 (Box 456, Folder 3)
        - London conference (1933), 386333 (Box 456, Folder 4)
        - Loose items, 386334 (Box 456, Folder 5)
        - MacArthur, Douglas, 386335 (Box 456, Folder 6-7)
        - MacLeish, Archibald, 386336 (Box 456, Folder 8)
        - Manpower, 386337 (Box 456, Folder 9)
        - Marshall-Eisenhower, 386338 (Box 456, Folder 10)
        - Marxism, 386339 (Box 456, Folder 11)
        - Morgenthau, Henry, 386340 (Box 456, Folder 12)
        - Movies, 386341 (Box 456, Folder 13)
        - Munich, 386342 (Box 456, Folder 14)
        - Mussolini, Benito, 386343 (Box 456, Folder 15)
        - National Labor Relations Board, 386344 (Box 457, Folder 1)
        - National Recovery Administration, 386345 (Box 457, Folder 2-6)
        - National Resources Planning Board, 386346 (Box 457, Folder 7)
        - Navy, 386347 (Box 457, Folder 8-9)
        - Nazi espionage, 386348 (Box 457, Folder 10)
        - Nazi-Soviet pact, 386349 (Box 457, Folder 11)
        - Negotiated peace, 386350 (Box 457, Folder 12)
        - Neutrality, 386351 (Box 458, Folder 1-2)
        - Neutrality Acts, 386352 (Box 458, Folder 3)
        - New Deal, 386353
          - 1939, 386354 (Box 458, Folder 4)
          - Communist Party, 386355 (Box 458, Folder 5-6)
          - Isolationism, 386356 (Box 458, Folder 7)
          - New Dealers, 386357 (Box 458, Folder 8)
          - Second New Deal, 386358 (Box 458, Folder 9-10)
          - Third New Deal, 386359 (Box 458, Folder 11)
          - Unhappy New Dealers, 386360 (Box 458, Folder 12)
          - General, 386361 (Box 459, Folder 1-2)
        - New York tradition, 386362 (Box 459, Folder 3)
        - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 386363 (Box 459, Folder 4)
        - Nineteen thirteen-Nineteen thirty-two, 386364 (Box 470, Folder 1-4)
        - Nineteen thirty-five-Nineteen forty-one; Nineteen forty-five, 386365 (Box 471, Folder 1-10)
        - North Africa, 386366 (Box 459, Folder 5)
        - Nye Committee, 386367 (Box 459, Folder 6)
        - Occupation policy, 386368 (Box 459, Folder 7)
        - Office of Price Administration, 386369 (Box 459, Folder 8)
        - Office of Strategic Services, 386370 (Box 459, Folder 9)
        - Office of War Information, 386371 (Box 459, Folder 10)
        - Office of War Mobilization, 386372 (Box 459, Folder 11)
        - Oil, 386373 (Box 459, Folder 12)
        - Opinion, 386374 (Box 459, Folder 13)
        - Pacific War, 386375 (Box 459, Folder 14)
        - Pacifism, 386376 (Box 459, Folder 15)
        - Palestine, 386377 (Box 460, Folder 1)
        - Pearl Harbor, 386378 (Box 460, Folder 2)
        - Perkins, Frances, 386379 (Box 460, Folder 3)
        - Philippines, 386380 (Box 460, Folder 4)
        - Planning, 386381 (Box 460, Folder 5)
        - Poland, 386382 (Box 460, Folder 6)
        - Politics, 386383 (Box 460, Folder 7)
        - Popular front, 386384 (Box 460, Folder 8-9)
        - Power policy, 386385 (Box 460, Folder 10)
        - Post-war planning, 386386 (Box 461, Folder 1-2)
        - Presidential campaigns, 386387
          - 1932, 386388 (Box 461, Folder 3)
          - 1940, 386389 (Box 461, Folder 4)
          - 1944, 386390 (Box 461, Folder 5)
        - Presidential elections, 386391
          - 1924, 386392 (Box 461, Folder 6)
          - 1928, 386393 (Box 461, Folder 7)
        - Price controls, 386394 (Box 461, Folder 8)
        - Pro-appeasement debate, 386395 (Box 461, Folder 9)
        - Progressives, 386396 (Box 461, Folder 10)
        - Purge (1938), 386397 (Box 461, Folder 11)
        - Quarantine speech, 386398 (Box 462, Folder 1-2)
        - Quebec, 386399 (Box 462, Folder 3)
        - Radicalism, 386400 (Box 462, Folder 4)
        - Recession, 386401 (Box 462, Folder 5)
        - Reciprocal trade, 386402 (Box 462, Folder 6)
        - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 386403 (Box 462, Folder 7-8)
        - Rediscovery of America, 386404 (Box 462, Folder 9-10)
        - Rendezvous with destiny, 386405 (Box 462, Folder 11)
        - Republicans, 386406
          - 1940, 386407 (Box 463, Folder 1)
          - Opposition, 386408 (Box 463, Folder 2)
          - Reaction, 386409 (Box 463, Folder 3)
          - Wartime party, 386410 (Box 463, Folder 4)
        - Revisionism (World War II), 386411 (Box 463, Folder 5)
        - Romania/Hungary, 386412 (Box 463, Folder 6)
        - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 386413 (Box 463, Folder 7)
        - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 386414
          - Fourth term, 386415 (Box 463, Folder 8)
          - Health, 386416 (Box 463, Folder 9)
          - Personality, 386417 (Box 463, Folder 10)
          - Wartime, 386418 (Box 463, Folder 11)
          - General, 386419 (Box 463, Folder 12)
        - Royal Visit (1939), 386420 (Box 463, Folder 13)
        - Rubber, 386421 (Box 464, Folder 1)
        - Rural Electrification Administration, 386422 (Box 464, Folder 2)
        - Sacco-Vanzetti case, 386423 (Box 464, Folder 3)
        - Science and technology, 386424 (Box 464, Folder 4)
        - Second front, 386425 (Box 464, Folder 5)
        - Sectoral policy, 386426 (Box 464, Folder 6)
        - Social theory, 386427 (Box 464, Folder 7)
        - Social work tradition, 386428 (Box 464, Folder 8)
        - Socialist Party, 386429 (Box 464, Folder 9)
        - Socialist Party/Communist Party, 386430 (Box 464, Folder 10)
        - South, 386431 (Box 464, Folder 11)
        - Southeast Asia, 386432 (Box 464, Folder 12)
        - Soviet espionage, 386433 (Box 464, Folder 13)
        - Spanish Civil War, 386434 (Box 464, Folder 14)
        - Stalin, Josef, 386435 (Box 465, Folder 1-2)
        - State Department, 386436 (Box 465, Folder 3-6)
        - Statistics, 386437 (Box 465, Folder 7)
        - Status of business, 386438 (Box 465, Folder 8)
        - Strikes, 386439 (Box 465, Folder 9)
        - Submarine war, 386440 (Box 465, Folder 10)
        - Tax/budget, 386441 (Box 465, Folder 11)
        - Tennessee Valley Authority, 386442 (Box 465, Folder 12-13)
        - Third term, 386443 (Box 465, Folder 14)
        - Trend left, 386444 (Box 465, Folder 15)
        - Tripartite agreement, 386445 (Box 465, Folder 16)
        - Truman, Harry S., 386446 (Box 465, Folder 17)
        - Tugwell, Rexford, 386447 (Box 465, Folder 18)
        - Unconditional surrender, 386448 (Box 466, Folder 1)
        - Unemployment, 386449 (Box 466, Folder 2)
        - U.S.S.R., 386450 (Box 466, Folder 3-6)
        - U.S.S.R/Germany, 386451 (Box 466, Folder 7)
        - Union Party, 386452 (Box 466, Folder 8)
        - United Kingdom, 386453 (Box 467, Folder 1-5)
        - United Nations, 386454 (Box 467, Folder 6)
        - Urban and state politics, 386455 (Box 467, Folder 7)
        - Vatican, 386456 (Box 467, Folder 8)
        - Vichy, 386457 (Box 467, Folder 9)
        - Wagner, LaFollette, Costigan, etc., 386458 (Box 467, Folder 10)
        - Wallace, Henry, 386459 (Box 467, Folder 11)
        - War Department, 386460 (Box 468, Folder 1)
        - War Production Board, 386461 (Box 468, Folder 2)
        - Wages and Hours Act, 386462 (Box 468, Folder 3)
        - Warm Springs, Georgia, 386463 (Box 468, Folder 4)
        - Welles mission, 386464 (Box 468, Folder 5)
        - West, 386465 (Box 468, Folder 6)
        - Women, 386466 (Box 468, Folder 7-8)
        - World Court, 386467 (Box 468, Folder 9-10)
        - World organizations, 386468 (Box 468, Folder 11)
        - World's Fair, 386469 (Box 468, Folder 12)
        - World War II, 386470
          - 1939, 386471 (Box 468, Folder 13)
          - 1940, 386472 (Box 468, Folder 14)
          - 1941, 386473 (Box 468, Folder 15)
          - Labor, 386474 (Box 468, Folder 16)
          - Literature, 386475 (Box 468, Folder 17)
          - Loyalty program, 386476 (Box 468, Folder 18)
          - Mobilization, 386477 (Box 468, Folder 19)
        - Writers in the 1930s, 386478 (Box 469, Folder 1)
        - Yalta, 386479 (Box 469, Folder 2-3)
        - Youth, 386480 (Box 469, Folder 4)
        - Yugoslavia, 386481 (Box 469, Folder 5)
      - Chapters, 386482
        - 22. Rediscovery of Democracy, 386483
          - Intellectuals and migration, 386484 (Box 472, Folder 1)
        - 23. FDR, 386485
          - Anna R., 386486 (Box 472, Folder 2)
          - Elliott R., 386487 (Box 472, Folder 3)
          - FDR, 386488 (Box 472, Folder 4-6)
          - FDR, Jr., 386489 (Box 472, Folder 7)
          - Mrs. R, 386490 (Box 472, Folder 8)
          - Miscellaneous on all Roosevelts, 386491 (Box 473, Folder 1)
        - 24. The Court Fight, 386492
          - Conservative Democrats, 386493 (Box 473, Folder 2)
          - FDR and Farley, 386494 (Box 473, Folder 3)
          - Jackson, 386495 (Box 473, Folder 4)
          - Jimmy Roosevelt, 386496 (Box 473, Folder 5)
          - Politics '37, 386497 (Box 473, Folder 6)
          - Politics '37-'38, 386498 (Box 473, Folder 7)
          - Republicans, 386499 (Box 473, Folder 8)
        - 25. Labor on the March, 386500
          - Communist Party and labor, 386501 (Box 473, Folder 9)
          - CIO, 386502 (Box 473, Folder 10)
          - Dies, 386503 (Box 473, Folder 11)
          - Dubinsky, 386504 (Box 473, Folder 12)
          - Economic situation, 386505 (Box 474, Folder 1)
          - FDR and labor, 386506 (Box 474, Folder 2)
          - Labor, 386507 (Box 474, Folder 3)
          - Labor and public opinion, 386508 (Box 474, Folder 4)
          - Labor violence, 386509 (Box 474, Folder 5)
          - LaFollette Committee, 386510 (Box 474, Folder 6)
          - Murphy, 386511 (Box 474, Folder 7)
          - NLRB, 386512 (Box 474, Folder 8)
          - Relations with business, 386513 (Box 474, Folder 9)
          - Sitdown strike, 386514 (Box 474, Folder 10)
          - Unemployment, 386515 (Box 474, Folder 11)
          - Wages--Hours Act, 386516 (Box 474, Folder 12)
          - WPA, 386517 (Box 474, Folder 13)
        - 26. The Spending Battle, 386518
          - Anti-monopoly campaign, 386519 (Box 475, Folder 1)
          - Causes of recession, 386520 (Box 475, Folder 2)
          - Economic thought, 386521 (Box 475, Folder 3)
          - Heavy industry, 386522 (Box 475, Folder 4)
          - Henderson, 386523 (Box 475, Folder 5)
          - Housing, 386524 (Box 475, Folder 6)
          - Keynes--Hansen, 386525 (Box 475, Folder 7)
          - LaFollette party, 386526 (Box 475, Folder 8)
          - NRA revival, 386527 (Box 475, Folder 9)
          - Power, 386528 (Box 475, Folder 10)
          - Price rigidity, 386529 (Box 476, Folder 1)
          - R. Whitney, 386530 (Box 476, Folder 2)
          - Railroads, 386531 (Box 476, Folder 3)
          - Regional authorities, 386532 (Box 476, Folder 4)
          - Spending fight, 386533 (Box 476, Folder 5)
          - W.O. Douglas, 386534 (Box 476, Folder 6)
        - 27. War Into the South, 386535
          - Byrnes, 386536 (Box 476, Folder 7)
          - Farm security, 386537 (Box 476, Folder 8)
          - Negroes, 386538 (Box 476, Folder 9-10)
          - Poll tax, lynching, etc., 386539 (Box 477, Folder 1)
          - Purge, 386540 (Box 477, Folder 2)
          - Relations with business, 386541 (Box 477, Folder 3)
          - Reorganization bill, 386542 (Box 477, Folder 4)
          - South, 386543 (Box 477, Folder 5)
          - Southern conservatives, 386544 (Box 477, Folder 6)
          - Southern economic report, 386545 (Box 477, Folder 7)
          - Southern radicals, 386546 (Box 477, Folder 8)
        - 28. Beyond the Purge, 386547
          - Administrative law, 386548 (Box 553, Folder 1)
          - Decline of Corcoran, 386549 (Box 553, Folder 2)
          - Interpretation of the New Deal, 386550 (Box 553, Folder 3)
          - McNutt, 386551 (Box 553, Folder 4)
          - Politics, 386552 (Box 553, Folder 5)
          - Welfare programs, 386553 (Box 553, Folder 6)
        - 29. War and the Third Term, 386554
          - 1939, 386555 (Box 553, Folder 7)
          - 1940 campaign, 386556 (Box 553, Folder 8)
          - 1940 election, 386557 (Box 553, Folder 9)
          - Aid to Britain, 386558 (Box 553, Folder 10)
          - Axis, 386559 (Box 553, Folder 11)
          - Business bribe, 386560 (Box 553, Folder 12)
          - Churchill, 386561 (Box 553, Folder 13)
          - Civil liberties, 386562 (Box 553, Folder 14)
          - Defense effort, 386563 (Box 478, Folder 1)
          - Democratic convention, 386564 (Box 478, Folder 2)
          - Destroyers, 386565 (Box 478, Folder 3)
          - Dilemma of isolationism, 386566 (Box 478, Folder 4)
          - Draft, 386567 (Box 478, Folder 5)
          - FDR, 1940, 386568 (Box 478, Folder 6)
          - FDR and European war, 386569 (Box 478, Folder 7)
          - Finnish war, 386570 (Box 478, Folder 8)
          - Foreign policy/public opinion, 386571 (Box 478, Folder 9)
          - Foreign purchasing, 386572 (Box 478, Folder 10)
          - France falls, 386573 (Box 478, Folder 11)
          - Hitler, 1940, 386574 (Box 478, Folder 12)
          - Interventionism, 386575 (Box 478, Folder 13)
          - Isolationism, 386576 (Box 478, Folder 14)
          - Jesse Jones, 386577 (Box 478, Folder 15)
          - Labor and defense, 386578 (Box 478, Folder 16)
          - Lewis in 1940, 386579 (Box 478, Folder 17)
          - Liberal Conservative, 386580 (Box 478, Folder 18)
          - Lindbergh, 386581 (Box 478, Folder 19)
          - M-Day, 386582 (Box 479, Folder 1)
          - Munich and after, 386583 (Box 479, Folder 2)
          - Pro-Nazi, 386584 (Box 479, Folder 3)
          - Public opinion, 386585 (Box 479, Folder 4)
          - Rearmament, 386586 (Box 479, Folder 5)
          - Refugee problem, 386587 (Box 479, Folder 6)
          - Republicans, 386588 (Box 479, Folder 7)
          - State Department, 386589 (Box 479, Folder 8)
          - Stimson-Knox appointments, 386590 (Box 479, Folder 9)
          - Third term movement, 386591 (Box 479, Folder 10)
          - Wallace candidacy, Hopkins, etc., 386592 (Box 479, Folder 11)
          - War impends, 386593 (Box 479, Folder 12)
          - Willkie, 386594 (Box 479, Folder 13)
        - 30. The Great Debate, 386595
          - Atlantic Charter, 386596 (Box 480, Folder 1)
          - Battle of Atlantic, 386597 (Box 480, Folder 2)
          - Declaration of emergency, 386598 (Box 480, Folder 3)
          - Defense effort, 386599 (Box 480, Folder 4)
          - Far East, 386600 (Box 480, Folder 5)
          - FDR, 386601 (Box 480, Folder 6)
          - Fund freezing, 386602 (Box 480, Folder 7)
          - Hopkins, 386603 (Box 480, Folder 8)
          - Impact of Nazi-Soviet pact, 386604 (Box 480, Folder 9)
          - Isolationism, 386605 (Box 480, Folder 10)
          - January-May 1941, 386606 (Box 480, Folder 11)
          - June 22, 1941, 386607 (Box 480, Folder 12)
          - Lend-Lease, 386608 (Box 480, Folder 13)
          - MacArthur in Philippines, 386609 (Box 480, Folder 14)
          - Pearl Harbor, 386610 (Box 480, Folder 15)
          - Vichy policy, 386611 (Box 480, Folder 16)
          - War!, 386612 (Box 480, Folder 17)
        - 31. The Politics of War, 386613
          - Anti-Hitler resistance, 386614 (Box 481, Folder 1)
          - B.E.W., 386615 (Box 481, Folder 2)
          - Big Three, 386616 (Box 481, Folder 3)
          - Cairo, 386617 (Box 481, Folder 4)
          - Casablanca, 386618 (Box 481, Folder 5)
          - Churchill, 386619 (Box 481, Folder 6)
          - Colonial problems, 386620 (Box 481, Folder 7)
          - CPUSA, 386621 (Box 481, Folder 8)
          - De Gaulle, 386622 (Box 481, Folder 9)
          - Far East, 386623 (Box 481, Folder 10)
          - FDR, 386624 (Box 481, Folder 11)
          - Foreign affairs, 386625 (Box 481, Folder 12)
          - German policy, 386626 (Box 482, Folder 1)
          - Germany, 386627 (Box 482, Folder 2)
          - Hull-Welles, 386628 (Box 482, Folder 3)
          - Italy, 386629 (Box 482, Folder 4)
          - Japan, 386630 (Box 482, Folder 5)
          - Manhattan Project, 386631 (Box 482, Folder 6)
          - Occupational problem, 386632 (Box 482, Folder 7)
          - Palestine--Arabs, 386633 (Box 482, Folder 8)
          - Poland, 386634 (Box 482, Folder 9)
          - Policy--North Africa, 386635 (Box 482, Folder 10)
          - Public opinion, 386636 (Box 482, Folder 11)
          - Quebec, 386637 (Box 482, Folder 12)
          - Relations with Soviet Union, 386638 (Box 483, Folder 1)
          - Second front, 386639 (Box 483, Folder 2)
          - Teheran, 386640 (Box 483, Folder 3)
          - Tito, 386641 (Box 483, Folder 4)
          - U.S.-France, 386642 (Box 483, Folder 5)
          - U.S.-U.S.S.R., 386643 (Box 483, Folder 6)
          - U.S.S.R.-U.S., 386644 (Box 483, Folder 7)
          - Unconditional surrender, 386645 (Box 484, Folder 1)
          - War aims discussion, 386646 (Box 484, Folder 2)
          - Willkie, 386647 (Box 484, Folder 3)
        - 32. The Home Front, 386648
          - 1942 election, 386649 (Box 484, Folder 4)
          - 1944 campaign, 386650 (Box 484, Folder 5)
          - Business and war, 386651 (Box 484, Folder 6)
          - Farmers--war, 386652 (Box 484, Folder 7)
          - FDR and Congress, 386653 (Box 484, Folder 8)
          - FDR--health, 386654 (Box 484, Folder 9)
          - FDR--home, 386655 (Box 484, Folder 10)
          - Labor and war, 386656 (Box 484, Folder 11)
          - Liberals, 386657 (Box 485, Folder 1)
          - New conservative, 386658 (Box 485, Folder 2)
          - OPA, 386659 (Box 485, Folder 3)
          - OWM, 386660 (Box 485, Folder 4)
          - Post-war planning, 386661 (Box 485, Folder 5)
          - Reaction, 386662 (Box 485, Folder 6)
          - Reconversion plans, 386663 (Box 485, Folder 7)
          - Republicans, 386664 (Box 485, Folder 8)
          - Vice Presidency, 386665 (Box 485, Folder 9)
          - Wallace, 386666 (Box 485, Folder 10)
          - Wartime atmosphere, 386667 (Box 485, Folder 11)
          - WPB, 386668 (Box 485, Folder 12)
        - 33. The Politics of Peace, 386669
          - FDR 1944-1945, 386670 (Box 486, Folder 1)
          - FDR--Death, 386671 (Box 486, Folder 2)
          - New Deal--unfinished business, 386672 (Box 486, Folder 3)
          - New Dealers after 1945, 386673 (Box 486, Folder 4)
          - Truman administration, 386674 (Box 486, Folder 5)
          - Yalta, 386675 (Box 486, Folder 6)
      - Outlines, 386676
        - FDR-Outline, 386677 (Box 487, Folder 1)
        - 1. Hundred Days, 386678 (Box 487, Folder 2)
        - 2. AAA, 386679 (Box 487, Folder 3)
        - 3. NRA, 386680 (Box 487, Folder 4)
        - 4. Monetary Policy, 386681 (Box 487, Folder 5)
        - 5. London Conference Reciprocal Trade, 386682 (Box 487, Folder 6)
        - 6. Relief/Public Works, 386683 (Box 487, Folder 7)
        - 7. Social Security, 386684 (Box 487, Folder 8)
        - 8. Conservation, 386685 (Box 487, Folder 9)
        - 9. Labor, 386686 (Box 487, Folder 10)
        - 10. Resurgence on the Right, 386687 (Box 487, Folder 11)
        - 11. Politics of Upheaval, 386688 (Box 487, Folder 12)
        - 12. Second New Deal, 386689 (Box 487, Folder 13)
        - 13. Supreme Court, 386690 (Box 487, Folder 14)
        - 14. Presidency, 386691 (Box 487, Folder 15)
        - 15. 1936, 386692 (Box 487, Folder 16)
        - Acknowledgments, 386693 (Box 488, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, 386694 (Box 488, Folder 2)
        - FDR, 386695 (Box 488, Folder 3)
        - Hyde Park, 386696 (Box 488, Folder 4)
        - Illustrations, 386697 (Box 488, Folder 5)
        - National Archives, 386698 (Box 488, Folder 6)
        - Outlines, 386699 (Box 488, Folder 7)
        - People to be consulted, 386700 (Box 488, Folder 8)
        - Preface, 386701 (Box 488, Folder 9)
    - Robert Kennedy and His Times, 386702
      - Africa, 386703 (Box 489, Folder 1)
      - Anti-Kennedy, 386704 (Box 489, Folder 2)
      - Attorney General, 386705
        - Campaign, 386706 (Box 489, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, 386707 (Box 489, Folder 4)
        - Press conference, 386708 (Box 489, Folder 5)
        - Publications, 386709 (Box 489, Folder 6)
        - Speeches and public appearances, 386710 (Box 489, Folder 7-9)
        - General, 386711 (Box 489, Folder 10)
      - Bedford-Stuyvesant, 386712 (Box 490, Folder 1)
      - Brazil, 386713 (Box 490, Folder 2)
      - Business, 386714 (Box 490, Folder 3)
      - Campaigns, 386715
        - 1946 (JFK for Congress), 386716 (Box 490, Folder 4)
        - 1952 (JFK for Senate), 386717 (Box 490, Folder 5)
        - 1956 (Stevenson for President), 386718 (Box 490, Folder 6)
        - 1960 (JFK for President), 386719
          - Civil rights, 386720 (Box 490, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence, 386721 (Box 490, Folder 8)
          - Democratic National Convention, 386722 (Box 490, Folder 9)
          - Publications, 386723 (Box 490, Folder 10)
          - Vice Presidential nomination, 386724 (Box 490, Folder 11)
          - General, 386725 (Box 490, Folder 12-13)
        - 1964 (RFK for Senate), 386726
          - Publications, 386727 (Box 490, Folder 14)
          - Speeches and public appearances, 386728 (Box 490, Folder 15)
          - General, 386729 (Box 491, Folder 1-2)
        - 1968 (RFK for President), 386730
          - Campaign strategy, 386731 (Box 491, Folder 3)
          - Decision to run, 386732 (Box 491, Folder 4-5)
          - Johnson, Lyndon, 386733 (Box 491, Folder 6-7)
          - McCarthy, Eugene, 386734 (Box 492, Folder 1)
          - Political issues, 386735 (Box 492, Folder 2)
          - Publicity, 386736 (Box 492, Folder 3)
          - Security, 386737 (Box 492, Folder 4)
          - Speeches, 386738 (Box 492, Folder 5)
          - Staff, 386739 (Box 492, Folder 6)
          - States, 386740 (Box 492, Folder 7-12)
          - Supporters, 386741 (Box 493, Folder 1)
          - Unruh, Jesse, 386742 (Box 493, Folder 2)
      - Catholicism, 386743 (Box 493, Folder 3)
      - Central Intelligence Agency and Castro, 386744 (Box 493, Folder 4)
      - Chavez, Cesar, 386745 (Box 493, Folder 5)
      - Chronologies, 386746 (Box 493, Folder 6)
      - Civil Rights, 386747
        - Attorney General, 386748 (Box 493, Folder 7-9)